okay honestly I've had enough what the fuck is wrong with y'all really three pieces three from
three people I have never met in my life from three publications that are supposed to be about
uplifting black people which is all I have dedicated my life to doing what hubris do I have
you people literally cannot stand that someone has studied and is speaking on what they study
that someone has read and is speaking on what they read you can't stand that someone loves us
that someone loves us so much that their passion is so exemplary and is exuding through the phone
that it touches people who literally have never felt love that much and they don't know how to
process it that's what you're feeling I want to send all the love to everyone who has shown me love
but you people who are continuing to attempt to break me down you will not break me you cannot
break me I am loved I am anointed I am touched I am working through the blood of our ancestors you
will not break me and it is so sad that you are so broken that this is the effort that you would take
to try and get some clout and you know what let's say I did get broken y'all would be the first ones
to be like see y'all be doing too much no big up to all my strong black women who are supporting other
strong black women and every other person supporting us we love you the rest of y'all can suck up